# KHAN MASROOF

# Software Developer

- \ +91-9149605834 @ khanmasroof33@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/khan-masroof-87a2a7a1/
- P Bemina Srinagar Jammu and Kashmir

#### **SUMMARY**

Tech-savvy WordPress Developer with over 3 years customizing online presence by implementing stunning layouts to maximize campaign reach. Goto resource for managing data presentation and back-end services for unique WordPress themeexperience. Pivotal in managing complex analytics, web traffic and campaign tracking systems to maintain organizational reach. Detailoriented approach to planning QA measures, API integration and deliverable launch.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Full Stack Wordpress Developer

05/2022 - Present

#### K21 Academy

London (Remote)

- Designed and developed customized website presentation to achieve optimized goals.
- Directed design, writing and production of page content to fulfill project demands and satisfy customer needs.
- Integrated third party forms, data, back-end services and specialized content to personalize WordPress theme layout and arrangement.
- · Conducted website performance tests, troubleshooting and upgrades.
- · Redesigned sites to enhance navigation and improve visual appeal.

#### Wordpress Developer

02/2020 - 03/2022

Parraypora Baghat

Srinagar

#### Bit by Bit Services

Srinagar

- · Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Created web models or prototypes using physical, interface, logical and data models.
- Designed visual and graphic images to use on multiple platforms.

# **EDUCATION**

Master of Computer Application (MCA): Computer Science And Programming	2020 - 2023
Cluster University Srinagar	Srinagar Jammu and Kashmir
Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA): Mathematics And Computer Science	2017 - 2020
Amar Singh College Cluster University Srinagar	Srinagar Jammu and Kashmir
Associate of Science: Engineering Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics	2015 - 2017
Boys Higher Secondary, Srinagar Jammu And Kashmir,	Srinagar Jammu and Kashmir
High School Diploma	2005 - 2014

## LANGUAGES

Salfia Muslim Institute

English	Native	••••	Kashmiri	Native	••••
Urdu	Native				



### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Microsoft Al: Artificial Intelligence Solutions License - 2019

The complete HTML,CSS and Javascript by Solo Learn

Complete paython Bootcamp with certification of Python X

The Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery on Udemy

#### **SKILLS**

Languages and Frameworkes  $\mbox{Wordpress} \cdot \mbox{Javacsript} \cdot \mbox{Python} \cdot \mbox{React} \cdot \mbox{Web Analytics Tools} \cdot \mbox{PHP} \cdot$ 

Web Applications and Server  $\cdot$  SEO  $\cdot$  WIX  $\cdot$  Database Skills  $\cdot$  HTML  $\cdot$  CSS